#!/bin/bash
Figures:

(11-20):
figures for phonons, selected ones?
?model for desorption

(0001)
#AIMD
?*comparison between surf at 0K and *surf at 300K preequalized


#crystal orbital based calculations
crystal table with frequencies (0001 and 11-20) and adsorption energies, compared to vasp results
(*)crystal optimized structures compared to vasp ones (B3LYP, PBE, MP2, HF?)
crystal tst for Df-H-4-2 reaction 

?#PIMD?
PIMD example trajectory

?#Embedding
[clusters for embedding? with and without additional point charges? maybe not at all..?]


*= (figure already exists =)
